mistupid.com 2014-05-17

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [policy@MIStupid.com](mailto:policy@MIStupid.com). 

At MIStupid.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by MIStupid.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, MIStupid.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
MIStupid.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Adbrite, Amazon, and others. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on MIStupid.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

MIStupid.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. mistupid.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>

**E-Mail**  
We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our discussion board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or newsletter registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. E-mail addresses are not shared with other organizations.

Send to Friend   Printable Page  [](http://www.addthis.com/bookmark.php)

Other Links:   
Contact, About
